insightexpressai.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | InsightExpress

The effective date for this Privacy Policy is November 11, 2011. 

InsightExpress, LLC (http://www.InsightExpress.com) has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [**TRUSTe's Data Collection Program**](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/3rd-party-data-collection/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at privacy@insightexpress.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [**TRUSTe here**](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). 

InsightExpress, LLC complies with the U.S. - E.U. & U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union and Switzerland. Information regarding the U.S. - E.U. & U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks can be found at: [**http://export.gov/safeharbor**](http://export.gov/safeharbor).

**Scope**

This Privacy Policy and the TRUSTe program addresses our use and disclosure of information we collect from Respondents to our surveys and/or contests. Respondents are users who respond to surveys and/or participate in sweepstakes that may be offered to you.

**Privacy Overview Respondents**

InsightExpress (http://www.InsightExpress.com) believes in and respects your privacy and the sanctity of information that may be provided. Further, as members of the ARF and CASRO, the North America associations of market research professionals, and the Mobile Marketing Association, the global association of the mobile marketing industry, we believe the use of information should be outlined for you as we have done so below. Additionally, InsightExpress is in compliance with HIPPA and COPPA privacy guidelines. InsightExpress is committed to respecting your privacy.

The information we collect is typically used in aggregate form to help companies understand marketplace needs as well as to create and deliver better products and services. We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information.

**Personal Information about Respondents**

In the course of responding to our surveys or sweepstakes, you may have the opportunity to voluntarily submit personally identifiable information (e.g., e-mail address or mobile phone number). InsightExpress maintains this information in a database, and may use this information to invite you to participate in future surveys, subject to agreement with the authoring and the respondent-providing client and your explicit opt-in to receive e-mail or mobile communications. Your decision to participate in future surveys is completely at your discretion. That is, you have no obligation to complete this or any future survey. By participating in a survey you understand and consent to this policy.

**Notice to Children and Young People**

InsightExpress does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. 

**Notice regarding health related topics/surveys**

Because facts about a person's demographic, health, health interest, and health care are private and sensitive, we know that you may have concerns about sharing information with us. When you enter health information on our survey forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). This Privacy statement is designed to answer your important questions about privacy.

**Sweepstakes**

Periodically we request information (typically e-mail address, mobile phone number or your mailing address if needed to mail a prize to you) from users to participate in sweepstakes. Sweepstakes participation is completely voluntary and users may choose whether or not to disclose this information. Your e-mail, mobile phone number or mailing address may be shared with the survey sponsor to notify winner(s) and award prizes. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give users notice and choice. Although we may use an intermediary to conduct sweepstakes, they may not employ users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purpose. 

**Use of Cookies**

To invite you to participate in surveys that may be of great interest to you and to enable you to use our service, we use "cookies" and, in some cases, local shared objects ("Flash Cookies"). "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer, and are commonly used by most Web sites to provide you with an enhanced experience. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored.  Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they enable us to understand the surveys you may have taken. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to inform you or prevent the use of cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able, depending upon the individual survey, to complete more than the first set of questions in a survey. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.  To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies [**click here**](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118). ****

If you would like to opt-out from receiving future web intercept survey invitations from InsightExpress, please click below:

[**http://ad.insightexpressai.com/adserver/optout.aspx?redir=http://www.opinion-central.com/optedout.asp**](http://ad.insightexpressai.com/adserver/optout.aspx?redir=http://www.opinion-central.com/optedout.asp)

When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer that will block us from sending you further surveys or sweepstakes invitations. Please note that if you remove cookies from your computer, you could receive another invitation since our technology will have no way of knowing if you requested to opt-out from these invitations.

**Log Files**

Like most Web sites, we log the use of our service. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks in order to administer the site, track aggregate movement, analyze trends, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Disclosure of Information**

When a Respondent supplies their personally identifiable information, such as an email address, during the course of completing a survey or sweepstakes it may be shared with a third party company who has been hired by us to provide services to help us with our business activities such as product fulfillment and sweepstakes management. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. Participation in these surveys or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

**Confidentiality**

We are sensitive to the privacy and security of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee absolute security as such information may be transmitted using the Internet, other public telecommunication networks, servers, hardware or software ("systems") that are not owned, operated, or controlled by us. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served to us. 

**Communications**  
Below are the instances when users may receive e-mail communications from our site. 

  * Survey Invitations

If a user wishes to participate in future surveys, we may request an e-mail address. Out of respect for our users' privacy, we also enable users to opt-out of future survey invitations by following the Opting-Out practices outlined below. 

  * Service Announcements

On rare occasions it may be necessary to issue a service related announcement (for instance, if our service is undergoing maintenance). These communications are not promotional in nature and users may not opt-out of these communications (although users can deactivate their account). 

**Customer Service Communications**

At a user's request, we may communicate via e-mail, chat, or telephone to answer service-related questions. E-mails and/or chats transcripts may be maintained by InsightExpress to provide assistance in resolving any inquiries. 

**Opt-Out Policy**

If you would like to opt-out from receiving future web intercept survey invitations from InsightExpress, please click below:

[**http://ad.insightexpressai.com/adserver/optout.aspx?redir=http://www.opinion-central.com/optedout.asp**](http://ad.insightexpressai.com/adserver/optout.aspx?redir=http://www.opinion-central.com/optedout.asp)

When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. Please note that if you remove cookies from your computer, you could receive another invitation since our technology will have no way of knowing if an invitation has been previously offered.

Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional communications or survey invitations may opt-out by replying to any received e-mail with "remove" or "unsubscribe" in the subject line, for mobile phone communications, reply with stop to the message or by contacting us as indicated below. 

**Maintaining, Updating, Deleting, or Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, e-mail or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done by e-mailing Customer Support at support@insightexpress.com or through one of the contact methods listed below. InsightExpress will respond to any access request within 30 days of submitting the request.

**Data Retention**

Users who respond to our surveys or contests will be assigned a unique user ID. The information associated with this unique ID, such as the last time you viewed or completed a survey, will be stored for a period of one year. In the event you elect to submit your email address upon completion of a survey or in connection with a sweepstakes, it will be stored and used to continue providing you surveys or sweepstakes which may be of interest to you until we are told otherwise. If you wish to request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at privacy@insightexpress.com.  Your email address will be retained on our ?Do Not Contact? list to ensure that we comply with your request.

Aggregated data, which does not give us the ability to contact or identify an individual, will be stored for analytical purposes for a legally allowable period.

We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations and resolve disputes.

**Links**

This Web site and surveys may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, InsightExpress, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post notification of those changes to this privacy statement on the homepage so users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users via e-mail prior to the changes taking effect. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/ deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also e-mail users who have opted to receive communications notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

**Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, site security, or other item, please contact us at: 

InsightExpress  
333 Ludlow Street  
Stamford, CT 06902  
Phone: 1.203.359.4174  
Fax: 1.203.359.4718  
E-Mail: support@insightexpress.com 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact our Privacy Department by e-mailing us at privacy@insightexpress.com or calling us at 1.203.406.3202. If they do not receive an acknowledgment of their inquiry or their inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, they should then contact [**TRUSTe here**](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve users concerns.

* * *

## Visitor/Client Privacy Policy

The effective date for this Privacy Policy is November 11, 2011. 

InsightExpress, LLC (http://www.InsightExpress.com) has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [**TRUSTe's program requirements**](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at privacy@insightexpress.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [**TRUSTe here**](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). 

InsightExpress, LLC complies with the U.S. - E.U. & U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union and Switzerland. Information regarding the U.S. - E.U. & U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks can be found at: [**http://export.gov/safeharbor**](http://export.gov/safeharbor).

**Scope**

This Privacy Policy and the TRUSTe program addresses our use and disclosure of information we collect from visitors to our Web site as well as from our Clients on our product platform.

Visitors are users who visit the website [**http://www.InsightExpress.com**](http://www.insightexpress.com/). Clients use our product platform in order to create surveys.

**Privacy Overview for our Clients**

**Information About Data that may be Provided by our Clients**

InsightExpress collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. We work with our Clients to help them provide notice to their customers concerning, the purpose for which personal information is collected 

InsightExpress has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data was provided by it Clients. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the InsightExpress' Client (the data controller). If the Client requests InsightExpress to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

InsightExpress will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. InsightExpress will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Information Collected about our Clients**

If you, as a client of ours, create surveys using our service, we request information from users within your organization who purchase our services via an order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, e-mail address, and shipping address, etc.) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date, etc.). This information is only used for billing purposes and to fill users' requests. If we have trouble processing an order, this information may be used to contact the user. 

**Use of Cookies**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer, and are commonly used by most Web sites to provide you with an enhanced experience. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Our cookies do not capture any personally identifying information. 

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to inform you or prevent the use of cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as sweepstakes or surveys, will be limited. 

**Log Files**

Like most Web sites, we log the use of our service. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks in order to administer the site, track aggregate movement, analyze trends, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Service Providers**

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as a credit card processor or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

**Confidentiality**

We are sensitive to the privacy and security of your personal information. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). However, we cannot guarantee absolute security as such information may be transmitted using the Internet, other public telecommunication networks, servers, hardware or software ("systems") that are not owned, operated, or controlled by us. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served to us. 

**Communications**  
Below are the instances when users may receive e-mail communications from our site. 

Newsletters  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we request an e-mail address. Out of respect for our users' privacy, we enable subscribers to opt-out of these communications by following the Opting-Out practices 

Service Announcements  
On rare occasions it may be necessary to issue a service related announcement (for instance, if our service is undergoing maintenance). These communications are not promotional in nature and users may not opt-out of these communications (although users can deactivate their account). 

**Customer Service Communications**

At a user's request, we may communicate via e-mail, chat, or telephone to answer service-related questions. E-mails and/or chats transcripts may be maintained by InsightExpress to provide assistance in resolving any inquiries. 

**Public Forums**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog, contact us at privacy@insightexpress.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Opt-Out Policy**

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter, promotional communications, or survey invitations may opt-out by replying to any received e-mail with "remove" or "unsubscribe" in the subject line, for mobile phone communications, reply with stop to the message or by contacting us as indicated below.

**Maintaining, Updating, Deleting, or Deactivating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, e-mail or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done by e-mailing Customer Support at support@insightexpress.com or by visiting https://www.insightexpress.com/ix/billinginfo.asp. We may also be reached using the contact information below. InsightExpress will respond to any access request provided within 30 days of submitting the request.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at privacy@insightexpress.com.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Links**

This Web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, InsightExpress, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site which includes any co-branded InsightExpress Web sites. 

**Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post notification of those changes to this privacy statement on the homepage so users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users via e-mail prior to the changes taking effect. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/ deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also e-mail users who have opted to receive communications notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

**Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, site security, or other item, please contact us at: 

InsightExpress  
333 Ludlow Street  
Stamford, CT 06902  
Phone: 1.203.359.4174  
Fax: 1.203.359.4718  
E-Mail: support@insightexpress.com 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact our Privacy Department by e-mailing us at privacy@insightexpress.com or calling us at 1.203.406.3202. If they do not receive an acknowledgment of their inquiry or their inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, they should then contact [**TRUSTe here**](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve users concerns.
